{
	"description": "Identify what's in the image",
	"type": "url",
	"deck": [
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/V4ibwkL",	"answers": ["蛇", "ヘビ", "青大将", "アオダイショウ", "snake", "japanese rat snake"], "comment": "蛇（へび） - snake\n青大将（あおだいしょう） - Japanese rat snake" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/PuuJVci",	"answers": ["李", "酸桃", "スモモ", "plum", "japanese plum"], "comment": "李（すもも） - (Japanese) plum\n酸桃（すもも） - (Japanese) plum" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/rKVbpnK",	"answers": ["ブルーベリー", "blueberry"], "comment": "ブルーベリー - blueberry" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/CX5mIpJ",	"answers": ["メロン", "melon"], "comment": "メロン - melon" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/YvK3h0F",	"answers": ["桃", "モモ", "peach"], "comment": "桃（もも） - peach" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/fpp5KHs",	"answers": ["西瓜", "水瓜", "スイカ", "watermelon"], "comment": "西瓜（すいか） - watermelon\n水瓜（すいか） - watermelon" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/VvG4nPp",	"answers": ["パイナップル", "pineapple"], "comment": "パイナップル - pineapple" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/HSbp7GS",	"answers": ["マンゴー", "mango"], "comment": "マンゴー - mango" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/98wzDIY",	"answers": ["葡萄", "ブドウ", "grape", "grapes"], "comment": "葡萄（ぶどう） - grape(s)" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/H1wUfAv",	"answers": ["苺", "イチゴ", "strawberry"], "comment": "苺（いちご） - strawberry" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/9Kyzt60",	"answers": ["梨", "ナシ", "pear"], "comment": "梨（なし） - pear" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/jeTbesb",	"answers": ["林檎", "リンゴ", "apple"], "comment": "林檎（りんご） - apple" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/wy2rLmT",	"answers": ["バナナ", "banana"], "comment": "バナナ - banana" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/cU5RMS0",	"answers": ["レモン", "lemon"], "comment": "レモン - lemon" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/XFb51Wh",	"answers": ["オレンジ", "orange"], "comment": "オレンジ - orange" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/Uk7c6JN",	"answers": ["猫", "ネコ", "cat"], "comment": "猫（ねこ） - cat" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/s6i9kkN",	"answers": ["犬", "イヌ", "dog"], "comment": "犬（いぬ） - dog" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/7LkAliV",	"answers": ["獅子", "ライオン", "シシ", "lion"], "comment": "獅子（しし） - lion" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/MN5Sypj",	"answers": ["象", "ゾウ", "elephant"], "comment": "象（ぞう） - elephant" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/Z8J8ySv",	"answers": ["麒麟", "騏驎", "キリン", "giraffe"], "comment": "麒麟（きりん） - giraffe" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/BqObT6S",	"answers": ["犀", "サイ", "rhinoceros", "rhino"], "comment": "犀（さい） - rhinoceros, rhino" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/aYpQR1j",	"answers": ["栗鼠", "リス", "squirrel"], "comment": "栗鼠（りす） - squirrel" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/FcAJ6xj",	"answers": ["鼠", "ネズミ", "rat"], "comment": "鼠（ねずみ） - rat" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/tjJrnki",	"answers": ["鼬", "イタチ", "weasel"], "comment": "鼬（いたち） - weasel" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/5PZedZ4",	"answers": ["猿", "サル", "monkey"], "comment": "猿（さる） - monkey" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/BWz1VU7",	"answers": ["水牛", "スイギュウ", "water buffalo"], "comment": "水牛（すいぎゅう） - water buffalo" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/88UW5Sh",	"answers": ["虎", "トラ", "tiger"], "comment": "虎（とら） - tiger" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/nbXSFp7",	"answers": ["豹", "ヒョウ", "leopard"], "comment": "豹（ひょう） - leopard" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/Kez97IZ",	"answers": ["牛", "ウシ", "cow"], "comment": "牛（うし） - cow" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/m6I7FID",	"answers": ["馬", "ウマ", "horse"], "comment": "馬（うま） - horse" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/RIqGQCj",	"answers": ["羊", "ヒツジ", "sheep"], "comment": "羊（ひつじ） - sheep" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/XNSIZAU",	"answers": ["山羊", "野羊", "ヤギ", "goat"], "comment": "山羊（やぎ） - goat" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/2DKtBrt",	"answers": ["豚", "ブタ", "pig"], "comment": "豚（ぶた） - pig" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/TGXKFH5",	"answers": ["猪", "イノシシ", "wild boar"], "comment": "猪（いのしし） - wild boar" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/sOHPTQU",	"answers": ["熊", "クマ", "bear"], "comment": "熊（くま） - bear" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/fMvC2WM",	"answers": ["白熊", "シロクマ", "北極熊", "ほっきょくぐま", "polar bear"], "comment": "白熊（しろくま） - polar bear\n北極熊（ほっきょくぐま） - polar bear" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/NqIT8CQ",	"answers": ["驢馬", "ロバ", "donkey", "ass"], "comment": "驢馬（ろば） - donkey, ass" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/5F2Ta93",	"answers": ["箆鹿", "ヘラジカ", "elk", "moose"], "comment": "箆鹿（へらじか） - elk; moose" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/Dz8kcbb",	"answers": ["鹿", "シカ", "deer"], "comment": "鹿（シカ） - deer" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/1sYJ0Hl",	"answers": ["狼", "オオカミ", "wolf"], "comment": "狼（おおかみ） - wolf" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/mcuaVyE",	"answers": ["狐", "キツネ", "fox"], "comment": "狐（きつね） - fox" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/E5zUfD4",	"answers": ["兎", "ウサギ", "野兎", "ノウサギ", "rabbit", "hare"], "comment": "兎（うさぎ） - rabbit\n野兎（のうさぎ） - hare" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/MTWuRRg",	"answers": ["蝙蝠", "コウモリ", "bat"], "comment": "蝙蝠（こうもり） - bat" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/cnQBg6m",	"answers": ["川獺", "獺", "カワウソ", "otter"], "comment": "川獺（かわうそ） - otter\n獺（かわうそ） - otter" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/P2kyZmt",	"answers": ["蟻食", "蟻食い", "アリクイ", "anteater"], "comment": "蟻食（ありくい） - anteater" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/VNGNjkd",	"answers": ["海豹", "アザラシ", "seal"], "comment": "海豹（あざらし） - seal" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/T0jkVQO",	"answers": ["河馬", "カバ", "hippopotamus", "hippo"], "comment": "河馬（かば） - hippopotamus, hippo" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/brwpWTB",	"answers": ["駱駝", "ラクダ", "camel"], "comment": "駱駝（らくだ） - camel" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/8wG1baZ",	"answers": ["穴熊", "アナグマ", "狢", "貉", "ムジナ", "badger"], "comment": "穴熊（あなぐま） - badger\n狢（むじな） - badger" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/nDYaNUL",	"answers": ["縞馬", "斑馬", "シマウマ", "zebra"], "comment": "縞馬（しまうま） - zebra" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/I3mcfCT",	"answers": ["烏", "鴉", "カラス", "crow", "raven"], "comment": "烏（からす） - crow, raven\n鴉（からす） - crow, raven" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/qbqDa5P",	"answers": ["鵲", "カササギ", "magpie"], "comment": "鵲（かささぎ） - magpie" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/FOcBr9B",	"answers": ["梟", "フクロウ", "owl"], "comment": "梟（ふくろう） - owl" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/8xUXnYD",	"answers": ["鸚鵡", "オウム", "parrot"], "comment": "鸚鵡（おうむ） - parrot" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/CO3C0Oa",	"answers": ["鸚哥", "インコ", "parakeet", "budgerigar", "budgie"], "comment": "鸚哥（いんこ） - parakeet, budgerigar, budgie" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/YPlXZNy",	"answers": ["鶴", "ツル", "丹頂", "タンチョウ", "crane", "red-crowned crane", "japanese crane"], "comment": "鶴（つる） - crane\n丹頂（たんちょう） - red-crowned crane, Japanese crane" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/IKZIAU7",	"answers": ["白鳥", "ハクチョウ", "swan"], "comment": "白鳥（はくちょう） - swan" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/pxAGYtb",	"answers": ["鴨", "カモ", "真鴨", "マガモ", "duck", "drake"], "comment": "鴨（かも） - duck, drake\n真鴨（まがも） - mallard" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/p61ksJ0",	"answers": ["家鴨", "アヒル", "domestic duck", "duck"], "comment": "家鴨（あひる） - domestic duck, duck" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/DguZKv4",	"answers": ["翡翠", "川蝉", "カワセミ", "kingfisher"], "comment": "翡翠（かわせみ） - kingfisher\n川蝉（かわせみ） - kingfisher" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/TDAHwH1",	"answers": ["鶏", "ニワトリ", "chicken", "hen"], "comment": "鶏（にわとり） - chicken, hen" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/QSj1Uy5",	"answers": ["鳩", "ハト", "pigeon"], "comment": "鳩（はと） - pigeon" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/UamdoFS",	"answers": ["鷲", "ワシ", "eagle"], "comment": "鷲（わし） - eagle" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/SqG3EdI",	"answers": ["孔雀", "クジャク", "peacock"], "comment": "孔雀（くじゃく） - peacock" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/7FnbE7a",	"answers": ["駝鳥", "ダチョウ", "ostrich"], "comment": "駝鳥（だちょう） - ostrich" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/MwLFT2I",	"answers": ["雀", "スズメ", "sparrow"], "comment": "雀（すずめ） - sparrow" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/9csShe4",	"answers": ["燕", "ツバメ", "swallow"], "comment": "燕（つばめ） - swallow" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/BkffLTX",	"answers": ["雉", "雉子", "キジ", "pheasant"], "comment": "雉（きじ） - pheasant\n雉子（きじ） - pheasant" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/vMLTFuP",	"answers": ["鷺", "サギ", "青鷺", "アオサギ", "heron"], "comment": "鷺（サギ） - heron\n青鷺（アオサギ） - (gray) heron" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/YoWc3ll",	"answers": ["目白", "メジロ", "white-eye", "japanese white-eye"], "comment": "目白（めじろ） - (Japanese) white-eye" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/x0o4JLs",	"answers": ["鶯", "ウグイス", "bush warbler", "japanese bush warbler"], "comment": "鶯（うぐいす） - (Japanese) bush warbler" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/Ja7cQqD",	"answers": ["蜂鳥", "ハチドリ", "hummingbird"], "comment": "蜂鳥（はちどり） - hummingbird" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/e0GMcI3",	"answers": ["ペンギン", "penguin"], "comment": "ペンギン - penguin" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/AjTgmiw",	"answers": ["赤松", "あかまつ", "japanese red pine", "japanese umbrella pine", "tanyosho pine"], "comment": "赤松（あかまつ） - Japanese red pine" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/z302SoV",	"answers": ["朝顔", "あさがお", "morning glory", "japanese morning glory"], "comment": "朝顔（あさがお） - (Japanese) morning glory" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/6vQX1kk",	"answers": ["紫陽花", "あじさい", "hydrangea", "bigleaf hydrangea", "french hydrangea"], "comment": "紫陽花（あじさい） - hydrangea" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/mQr8mei",	"answers": ["菖蒲", "あやめ", "iris"], "comment": "菖蒲（あやめ） - (Japanese) iris" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/tuJL6ZN",	"answers": ["銀杏", "公孫樹", "鴨脚樹", "いちょう", "ginkgo", "gingko", "maidenhair tree"], "comment": "銀杏（いちょう） - ginkgo, maidenhair tree" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/yBIWGD6",	"answers": ["大葉子", "おおばこ", "plantain"], "comment": "大葉子（おおばこ） - (Asiatic) plantain" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/dtyIOCr",	"answers": ["弟切草", "おとぎりそう", "hypericum erectum"], "comment": "弟切草（おとぎりそう） - hypericum erectum" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/agRd8lB",	"answers": ["鬼胡桃", "おにぐるみ", "japanese walnut", "manchurian walnut"], "comment": "鬼胡桃（おにぐるみ） - Japanese walnut, Manchurian walnut" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/GxqGa04",	"answers": ["橄欖", "かんらん", "chinese white olive"], "comment": "橄欖（かんらん） - Chinese white olive" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/eXfKJjg",	"answers": ["楓", "槭樹", "かえで", "maple", "maple tree"], "comment": "楓（かえで） - maple (tree)\n槭樹（かえで） - maple (tree)" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/J7eunu5",	"answers": ["燕子花", "杜若", "かきつばた", "rabbit-ear iris", "japanese iris"], "comment": "燕子花（かきつばた） - rabbit-ear iris, Japanese iris\n杜若（かきつばた） - rabbit-ear iris, Japanese iris" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/vnI9isA",	"answers": ["桂", "かつら", "katsura", "japanese judas tree"], "comment": "桂（かつら） - katsura, Japanese Judas tree" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/mEw3br7",	"answers": ["桔梗", "ききょう", "balloon flower", "chinese bellflower", "platycodon grandiflorum"], "comment": "桔梗（ききょう） - balloon flower, Chinese bellflower" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/HMf4KEa",	"answers": ["菊", "きく", "chrysanthemum"], "comment": "菊（きく） - chrysanthemum" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/0XiFGiA",	"answers": ["金木犀", "きんもくせい", "fragrant olive"], "comment": "金木犀（きんもくせい） - fragrant olive" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/j0ZkBYf",	"answers": ["樟", "楠", "くすのき", "くす", "camphor tree", "camphorwood", "camphor laurel"], "comment": "樟（くすのき） - camphor tree, camphorwood, camphor laurel\n楠（くすのき） - camphor tree, camphorwood, camphor laurel" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/GKbuPP0",	"answers": ["梔子", "くちなし", "しし", "cape jasmine", "cape jessamine", "gardenia"], "comment": "梔子（くちなし） - gardenia, Cape jasmine" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/nTbPpOz",	"answers": ["櫟", "橡", "椚", "くぬぎ", "つるばみ", "くのぎ", "sawtooth oak"], "comment": "櫟（くぬぎ） - sawtooth oak" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/brgNB5Y",	"answers": ["栃", "橡", "栃の木", "とちのき", "とち", "japanese horse-chestnut", "japanese horse chestnut"], "comment": "橡（とちのき） - Japanese horse-chestnut\n栃（とちのき） - Japanese horse-chestnut" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/8lWTbur",	"answers": ["黒松", "くろまつ", "black pine", "japanese black pine"], "comment": "黒松（くろまつ） - (Japanese) black pine" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/5Lbcsu9",	"answers": ["黒百合", "くろゆり", "black lily", "kamchatka lily", "kamchatka fritillary"], "comment": "黒百合（くろゆり） - Kamchatka lily, Kamchatka fritillary" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/VfI34Za",	"answers": ["桑", "くわ", "mulberry"], "comment": "桑（くわ） - mulberry" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/PSDalGJ",	"answers": ["月桂樹", "げっけいじゅ", "laurel", "bay laurel", "bay tree", "sweet bay", "laurel tree"], "comment": "月桂樹（げっけいじゅ） - (sweet bay) laurel (tree)" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/41i250C",	"answers": ["欅", "けやき", "槻", "つき", "keyaki", "japanese zelkova"], "comment": "欅（けやき） - keyaki, Japanese zelkova\n槻（つき） - keyaki, Japanese zelkova" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/FopaOe7",	"answers": ["コスモス", "秋桜", "あきざくら", "cosmos"], "comment": "コスモス - cosmos\n秋桜（あきざくら） - cosmos" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/zAFPRmb",	"answers": ["榊", "さかき", "sakaki"], "comment": "榊（さかき） - sakaki" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/WJy7Xg6",	"answers": ["桜", "さくら", "cherry tree", "cherry blossom"], "comment": "桜（さくら） - (Japanese) cherry tree, cherry blossom" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/xA6Zpx0",	"answers": ["山茶花", "さざんか", "sasanqua"], "comment": "山茶花（さざんか） - sasanqua" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/NfN6eOp",	"answers": ["百日紅", "猿滑", "さるすべり", "ひゃくじつこう", "crape myrtle"], "comment": "百日紅（さるすべり・ひゃくじつこう） - crape myrtle\n猿滑（さるすべり） - crape myrtle" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/ufhuVxd",	"answers": ["石南花", "石楠花", "しゃくなげ", "rhododendron"], "comment": "石南花（しゃくなげ） - rhododendron\n石楠花（しゃくなげ） - rhododendron" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/vyF5sFL",	"answers": ["水仙", "すいせん", "daffodil", "narcissus"], "comment": "水仙（すいせん） - narcissus, daffodil" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/UJagNSv",	"answers": ["杉", "すぎ", "japanese cedar", "cryptomeria"], "comment": "杉（すぎ） - Japanese cedar, cryptomeria" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/yk0lLWT",	"answers": ["鈴蘭", "すずらん", "lily of the valley", "lily-of-the-valley"], "comment": "鈴蘭（すずらん） - lily of the valley" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/hzg3pzv",	"answers": ["菫", "すみれ", "violet"], "comment": "菫（すみれ） - violet" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/W7g13HM",	"answers": ["染井吉野", "そめいよしの", "yoshino cherry"], "comment": "染井吉野（そめいよしの） - Yoshino cherry" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/Co6OZRd",	"answers": ["蒲公英", "たんぽぽ", "ほこうえい", "dandelion"], "comment": "蒲公英（たんぽぽ） - dandelion" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/khvfEP6",	"answers": ["躑躅", "つつじ", "azalea"], "comment": "躑躅（つつじ） - azalea" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/IWHVls5",	"answers": ["椿", "つばき", "camellia", "common camellia", "camellia japonica"], "comment": "椿（つばき） - (common) camellia" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/nfuYyXe",	"answers": ["薺", "なずな", "shepherd's purse"], "comment": "薺（なずな） - shepherd's purse" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/Cut4YIC",	"answers": ["棗", "なつめ", "jujube", "chinese date", "red date"], "comment": "棗（なつめ） - jujube, Chinese date, red date" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/FOO4Ut4",	"answers": ["撫子", "瞿麦", "なでしこ", "dianthus", "pink"], "comment": "撫子（なでしこ） - Dianthus, pink\n瞿麦（なでしこ・くばく） - Dianthus, pink" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/6k5Zo3D",	"answers": ["庭漆", "にわうるし", "tree of heaven"], "comment": "庭漆（にわうるし） - tree of heaven" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/aD0ax20",	"answers": ["野薔薇", "のいばら", "のばら", "multiflora rose", "japanese rose", "baby rose"], "comment": "野薔薇（のいばら） - multiflora rose, (Japanese) rose, baby rose" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/Nz1U71s",	"answers": ["繁縷", "はこべ", "はこべら", "chickweed", "stitchwort"], "comment": "繁縷（はこべ） - chickweed, stitchwort" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/M7T6FGA",	"answers": ["蓮", "はす", "はちす", "lotus", "sacred lotus", "indian lotus"], "comment": "蓮（はす・はちす） - (Indian) lotus, sacred lotus" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/7SxQXfu",	"answers": ["花水木", "はなみずき", "flowering dogwood"], "comment": "花水木（はなみずき） - flowering dogwood" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/mSE4knH",	"answers": ["薔薇", "ばら", "しょうび", "そうび", "rose"], "comment": "薔薇（ばら・しょうび・そうび） - rose" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/hDFxNhi",	"answers": ["柊", "疼木", "ひいらぎ", "ひらぎ", "holly olive", "false holly"], "comment": "柊（ひいらぎ） - holly olive, false holly\n柊木（ひいらぎ） - holly olive, false holly" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/9E0n3n3",	"answers": ["彼岸花", "ひがんばな", "red spider lily", "cluster amaryllis"], "comment": "彼岸花（ひがんばな） - red spider lily, cluster amaryllis" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/qG3Ff4M",	"answers": ["雛罌粟", "雛芥子", "ひなげし", "red poppy", "common poppy", "coquelicot"], "comment": "雛罌粟（ひなげし） - red poppy, common poppy, coquelicot\n雛芥子（ひなげし） - red poppy, common poppy, coquelicot" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/Iaj8PlG",	"answers": ["檜", "桧", "ひのき", "ひ", "hinoki", "hinoki cypress", "japanese cypress"], "comment": "檜（ひのき） - hinoki cypress, Japanese cypress" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/BgiVUF1",	"answers": ["向日葵", "ひまわり", "sunflower"], "comment": "向日葵（ひまわり） - sunflower" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/SrgARSa",	"answers": ["風信子", "ヒヤシンス", "ふうしんし", "hyacinth"], "comment": "風信子（ヒヤシンス・ふうしんし） - hyacinth" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/s0J5zux",	"answers": ["昼顔", "ひるがお", "bindweed", "japanese bindweed"], "comment": "昼顔（ひるがお） - (Japanese) bindweed" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/vtPsdqx",	"answers": ["藤", "ふじ", "wisteria", "wistaria"], "comment": "藤（ふじ） - wisteria, wistaria" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/RSChT9a",	"answers": ["橅", "山毛欅", "椈", "ぶな", "beech", "siebold's beech"], "comment": "橅（ぶな） - (Siebold's) beech\n山毛欅（ぶな） - (Siebold's) beech\n椈（ぶな） - (Siebold's) beech" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/fRzHAtf",	"answers": ["紅花", "べにばな", "こうか", "safflower", "dyer's safflower", "carthamus tinctorius"], "comment": "紅花（べにばな・こうか） - safflower, dyer's safflower, carthamus tinctorius" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/dUdrV5c",	"answers": ["鳳仙花", "ほうせんか", "garden balsam", "balsam"], "comment": "鳳仙花（ほうせんか） - (garden) balsam" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/bsiz5Z1",	"answers": ["酸漿", "鬼灯", "ほおずき", "ほおづき", "ぬかずき", "かがち", "winter cherry", "chinese lantern plant", "ground-cherry"], "comment": "酸漿（ほおずき） - winter cherry, Chinese lantern plant, ground-cherry\n鬼灯（ほおずき） - winter cherry, Chinese lantern plant, ground-cherry" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/VQK1Ycr",	"answers": ["牡丹", "ぼたん", "tree peony", "moutan"], "comment": "牡丹（ぼたん） - tree peony, moutan" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/3saMIU6",	"answers": ["木槿", "むくげ", "もくげ", "rose of sharon"], "comment": "木槿（むくげ・もくげ） - rose of Sharon" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/p4g4l7W",	"answers": ["樅", "もみ", "japanese fir", "momi fir"], "comment": "樅（もみ） - Japanese fir, momi fir" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/PLoTGJN",	"answers": ["山吹", "やまぶき", "kerria", "japanese yellow rose"], "comment": "山吹（やまぶき） - kerria, Japanese yellow rose" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/UyquT3N",	"answers": ["夕顔", "ゆうがお", "bottle gourd"], "comment": "夕顔（ゆうがお） - bottle gourd" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/hLKKnuC",	"answers": ["百合", "ゆり", "lily"], "comment": "百合（ゆり） - lily" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/ZmkQvCU",	"answers": ["夜顔", "よるがお", "moonflower"], "comment": "夜顔（よるがお） - moonflower" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/TwGkBEN",	"answers": ["蘭", "らん", "orchid"], "comment": "蘭（らん） - orchid" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/yFNGWOd",	"answers": ["竜胆", "りんどう", "りゅうたん", "gentian", "autumn bellflower"], "comment": "竜胆（りんどう・りゅうたん） - (Japanese) gentian, autumn bellflower" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/YyI3tMi",	"answers": ["蓮華草", "れんげそう", "ゲンゲ", "レンゲ", "chinese milk vetch"], "comment": "蓮華草（れんげそう） - Chinese milk vetch" },
		{"question": "https://imgur.com/lsWyFx6",	"answers": ["団栗", "どんぐり", "acorn"], "comment": "団栗（どんぐり） - acorn" }
	]
}


